Imaad Uwaiz

http://imaduwaiz.github.io

Email: imaaduwaiz@gmail.com

Mobile: +971588289287 Address: Dubai, UAE.



Profile

Innovative, task-driven professional with good experience in WordPress, SEO, CMS, SEM, Google Ads, Web Development, Graphic/UI Designing, Operation Manager, Multi-Tasking, and handling the smooth workflow of the company. Fluent in English with good communication and interpersonal skills. A Fast learner with strong time management and multi-tasking skills. Strong work ethic in a team or individual setting to drive product success and process efficiency while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.

EDUCATION

B.E in Computer Science and Engineering

Visvesvaraya Technological University

Dr. T. TIT

Aug 2017 - Sep 2021

Experience

* E-Commerce Executive (Operation Manager)

Lablaab Electronic Trading L.L.C

Dubai

Nov 2021 - Present

- Analyze and evaluate the company's online retail performance and Maintain the website and App.
- Collaborating with the customers for wholesale orders.
- Handling Marketing Operations of the company.
- Handling overall operation of the company from the time of Order till delivery of the products.
- Monitoring the orders on daily basis with DHL, Aramex, SMSA, Shippa, and Quick Up shipping companies.

*SEO / Google Ads / CMS

Lablaab Electronic Trading L.L.C

Dubai

Nov 2021 - Present

• Improving the site traffic through SEO, Keyword Research using Semrush and, Rank Math.

- Worked on the improvements of Backlinks, Directory Submition, customer experience, analyzed website performance, and stayed up to date with current industry trends.
- · Collaborating with the management team and creating Google Ads Campaigns.
- Inventory Management on platforms like Noon, Carrefour, Amazon.

* Graphic Design / Social Media

Nov 2021 - Present

Dubai

Lablaab Electronic Trading L.L.C

- Designing English and Arabic Post and Creating Ads on Instagram and Facebook.
- Designing the sliders and banners for the website and Application using Figma, Illustrator and Photoshop
- Handling Social media accounts of the company.
- Making Dynamic videos for product advertisement.
- · Creating and Editing Product Unboxing Video

Internship

- *CCNA Cisco Module 1 & Module 2 (4 months)
- *TCS IT Employability program (1 month)
- *Pirple Web development internship (2months)
- *RPA Robotic process automation in Blue Prisim

Skills

*Technical skills: Google Ads, HTML, CSS, Python, Analytical Skills,

Multi-tasking, Content Management

^{*}Softwares: Wordperss, Figma, Illustrator, Photoshop, Resolve

Personal Details

Name: Imaad Uwaiz Nationality: Indian

Visa status: Employment Visa

Visa Expiry: 2024 Religion: Islam

Marital Status: Un-Married

Achivements

- Winner of a contest conducted by **Discover Channel India**
- Winner of a contest conducted by **Animal Planet**
- Winner of a contest conducted by Nikon Asia
- Won many a contest in **Engineering College**

Hobbies

Photography, Cooking, Traveling, Videography, Developing new skills

Language

English

Hindi

Urdu

Kannada

Self Declaration

I hereby declare that all the above information is correct and accurate. I solemnly declare that all the information furnished in this document is free of errors to the best of my knowledge. I hereby declare that all the information contained in this resume/CV is per facts or truth to my knowledge.

(IMAAD UWAIZ)